YOUR NEXT IDEA STARTS HERE.
WELCOME TO 0.6.1.
SIDEBAR TABS. IN REACH.
YOUR COLORS. ON TAP.
ASSETS YOU CAN SEE.
ICONS. READY TO USE.
TYPE WITHOUT LIMITS.
NEW TYPOGRAPHY CONTROLS.
OPENTYPE. DIALED IN.
TRACKING. KERNING. BASELINE.
THE NEW LASSO PEN.
CURVES YOU CONTROL.
MORE PIXEL SELECTION OPTIONS.
SELECT. REFINE. ISOLATE.
PLUGINS. MORE POSSIBILITIES.
ONE CLICK. NEW LOOK.
OMARCHY THEME SYNC.
YOUR DESKTOP. YOUR STUDIO.
CLOUD. SHARE THE WORK.
YOUR PROJECTS. ANYWHERE.
FEEDBACK. BACK IN THE APP.
SMOOTH MOTION PLAYBACK.
MAKE EVERY FRAME COUNT.
BRUSH UI. UP TO 4.56×.
KEEP UP WITH YOUR IDEAS.
BUILT-IN AGENTIC HARNESS.
GIVE IT THE BRIEF.
RIGHT INSIDE YOUR CANVAS.
TOOLS INTO ACTION.
WATCH THE WORK TAKE SHAPE.
REAL OBJECTS. LIVE ON CANVAS.
TAKE OVER. MAKE IT YOURS.
START WITH YOUR DESIGN.
ASK FOR A CHANGE.
TURN CONTEXT INTO DESIGN.
SEE THE RESULT.
KEEP EVERYTHING EDITABLE.
YOUR AGENT. YOUR STUDIO.
YOUR NEXT IDEA. BUILT.
MORE CONTROL.
MORE POSSIBILITIES.
LESS WAITING.